嘿  维罗收到那张字条了么
Hey, did Willow get the note?
- 对  她收到了  - 她高兴么
- Yeah, she did, but... - Was she happy?
- 呃  其实她  -嘘  嘘  嘘  嘘
- Well, yeah, she was... - shh shh shh shh.
我只要知道她不会再粘着我了就好
All I needed to know is that she's off my scent.
你干的太漂亮了
You have served your purpose.
嘿  维罗
Hey, Willow.
维罗  维罗  维罗
Willow Willow Willow.
我听说你在储物柜里收到了一张小字条
I heard you got a little note in your locker.
我确实收到了
I did.
我打赌你挺兴奋的吧  哈
I bet you're pretty excited about that, huh?
我就说追随着彩虹总会发现你心所属的嘛
I say chase this rainbow and see where it takes you.
- 呃  乔伊  - 玛蒂
- Um, Joey... - Maddie.
现在别掺和
Not now.
我已经等这一刻
I've been waiting for this moment
等了很久了
for a long time.
我实在是憋不住了
I just can't take it anymore.
乔伊·鲁尼暗恋着我
Joey Rooney's my secret admirer!
到底发生什么了
What is happening?
哎呀
Yeah.
呃 我想我们仨最好
Uh, I think it's best that the three of us
找个安全的地方解释清楚吧
talk about this in a safe place.